<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on MercNet</title>
    <link>https://mercnet.jaredisgray.com/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on MercNet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mercnet.jaredisgray.com/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>News: Gav Bleuel - Most Clones of Single Sophont in History</title>
      <link>https://mercnet.jaredisgray.com/news/new-gavclones/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mercnet.jaredisgray.com/news/new-gavclones/</guid>
      <description>Gav Bleuel - Most Clones of Single Sophont in History 950 million Gav clones were unleashed on the galaxy, making blue-haired Caucasian men who like Guinness the single largest demographic in the galaxy. Sources claim the feat is somehow related to an alleged conspiracy by the Wormgate Corporation.
Bio The handsome, blue-haired scientist is one of the oldest humans in the Galaxy, if you&amp;rsquo;re counting from birth dates. Born in the late 20th century, &amp;ldquo;Gav&amp;rdquo; studied nuclear physics (earning a Ph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News: Ob&#39;enn On The March Again</title>
      <link>https://mercnet.jaredisgray.com/news/news-obennloose/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mercnet.jaredisgray.com/news/news-obennloose/</guid>
      <description>Ob&amp;rsquo;enn On The March Again Tausennigan Ob’enn, once contained in their own system by an alliance fleet blockade of their wormgate, have taken advantage of the teraport to facilitate a return to their expansionist war on multiple fronts.
Tausennigan Kss&amp;rsquo;thrata evacuated their entire planet’s population to locations unknown using teraports just in time to avoid a genocidal invasion by the Ob’enn. With their longstanding enemy out of the way and their home system secured, the massive Ob’enn war machine has been redirected outside their home system to support new wars against those who once held their ambitions in check.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News: Wormgates Shut Down in 20k Systems</title>
      <link>https://mercnet.jaredisgray.com/news/news-wormgatesshutdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mercnet.jaredisgray.com/news/news-wormgatesshutdown/</guid>
      <description>Wormgates Shut Down in 20k Systems Twenty thousand wormgates suddenly shut down yesterday, leaving major population centers accessable only via teraport. Whole sectors of the galaxtic economy have been crippled. Wormgate Corp blames the shutdowns on destruction of infrastructure from Admiral Breya Andreyasn’s unprovoked attack. Other sources claim that this is retaliation in an attempt to blackmail galactic powers into punishing the Admiral and participating allied governments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News: Teraport Wars</title>
      <link>https://mercnet.jaredisgray.com/news/news-teraportwars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mercnet.jaredisgray.com/news/news-teraportwars/</guid>
      <description>Teraport Wars Since the teraport was suddenly released into the public domain 3 months ago, most governments and large companies have been scrambling to implement TAD systems and retrofit teraports onto their ships. Not everyone has them yet. Civilian vessels and poorer systems may still lack TAD, or only have short range/partial coverage. Most civilian vessels don’t have teraports yet.
Wars have erupted galaxy-wide as enemies and opportunists attempt to take advantage of the situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News: Wormgate Corporation Attacked</title>
      <link>https://mercnet.jaredisgray.com/news/news-wormgateattacked/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mercnet.jaredisgray.com/news/news-wormgateattacked/</guid>
      <description>Wormgate Corporation Attacked Rumors are circulating that a fleet under the command of Admiral Breya Andreyasn attacked major holdings of the Wormgate Corporation for unknown reasons. Spokespeople for the Wormgate Corp claim it was an unprovoked first strike.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
